DC Showcase: Jonah Hex is a animation, action, western
film directed by Joaquim Dos Santos.
When a ruthless brothel madame murders Jonah Hex's current quarry,
the disfigured bounty hunter plans to make her pay.
Jonah Hex (voice), played by Thomas Jane.
Madame Lorraine (voice), played by Linda Hamilton.
Young Man / Bartender (voice), played by Jason Marsden.
Red Doc (voice), played by Michael Rooker.
Bar Girl (voice), played by Michelle Trachtenberg.
Jonah Hex is a 2010 American Western superhero film based on
the DC Comics character of the same name.
Directed by Jimmy Hayward (in his live-action debut) from a screenplay by Neveldine/Taylor, the film stars Josh Brolin in
the title role, alongside John Malkovich, Megan Fox, Michael Fassbender, Will Arnett and Michael Shannon.
Produced by Legendary Pictures, Andrew Lazar's Mad Chance Productions and Akiva Goldsman's
Weed Road Pictures, the film was released on June 18, 2010, by Warner Bros.
It was a commercial failure, having grossed only $11
million against a budget of $47 million.
It received generally negative reviews from critics.